campuslogic.com 2019-10-31

# CampusLogic Privacy and Cookie Policy Last Updated: 6/12/18

 CampusLogic Privacy and Cookie Policy
 Last Updated: 6/12/18
 CampusLogic, Inc. (“CampusLogic,” “we,” and “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit
 and use this website www.campuslogic.com (the “Site”) and/or the software applications (the “Applications”)
 provided by CampusLogic, together the “Services.” This Privacy and Cookie Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) describes
 how CampusLogic collects, uses, and shares personal information. Please read the following information carefully
 to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it.
1. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
 CampusLogic collects and retains personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email
 addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by you to CampusLogic through the Site and/or Services. We will only
 process your personal information in accordance with applicable data protection and privacy laws.
 If you registered to use the Services, you will have been asked to click to agree to provide this information in order
 to access our services or otherwise view our content. If you do not agree to our use of your personal information
 in line with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Services. By accessing and using our Site or by clicking “I
 accept” prior to your registration to the CampusLogic Services, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure
 of your personal information by CampusLogic as described in this Privacy Policy.
 We collect information about you in the following ways:
 Information You Give Us. This includes the personal information you provide when you register to use our Services,
 including your name, postal address, email address, and other personal and unique information provided to
 CampusLogic based on your submissions and responses to questions asked of you throughout the Services.
 Information We Get From Others. We may also get information about you from other sources, for example, your
 academic institution’s department of financial aid or the Department of Education. We may add this information
 to personal information we get from your use of the Services.
 Information Automatically Collected. We automatically log information about you and your computer or mobile
 device when you access our Site and/or Services. Please refer to the sections on Cookies/ Tracking Technology
 below.
2. COOKIE/TRACKING TECHNOLOGY
 What are cookies?
 We may collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on the hard drive of your computer
 or mobile device by a website. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser)
 and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer or mobile device until you delete them) to provide you with
 a more personal and interactive experience in the Services.
 Cookies We Use.
 Our Services use the following types of cookies for the purposes set out below:

   Type of cookie                  Purpose
   Essential Cookies               These cookies are essential to provide you with services available through our
                                   Site and to enable you to use some of its features. For example, they allow you
                                   to log in to secure areas of our Services. Without these cookies, the services that
                                   you have asked for cannot be provided, and we only use these cookies to provide
                                   you with those services. These cookies are only used for the duration of your
                                   session accessing the CampusLogic services and are removed following
                                   completion of the session.
   Functionality Cookies           These cookies allow us to remember choices you make when you use our
                                   Services, such as remembering your login details. The purpose of these cookies
                                   is to provide you with a more personal experience and to avoid you having to re-
                                   enter your preferences every time you visit our Services.
   Analytics   and   Performance These cookies are used to collect information about traffic to our Site and how
   Cookies                         users use our Services. The information gathered does not identify any individual
                                   visitor. The information is aggregated and anonymous. It includes the number of
                                   visitors to Site, the pages they visited on our Site, whether they have visited our
                                   Site before, and other similar information. We use this information to help
                                   operate our Site more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information and
                                   to monitor the level of activity on our Site.
                                   We use Google Analytics for this purpose. Google Analytics uses its own cookies.
                                   It is only used to improve how [our Site/Application(s)/Services] works. You can
                                   find out more information about Google Analytics cookies here:
                                   https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCooki
                                   es.
                                   You can find out more about how Google protects your data here:
                                   www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html.
                                   You can prevent the use of Google Analytics relating to your use of [our
                                   Site/Application(s)/Services] by downloading and installing the browser plugin
                                   available via this link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB.
Disabling Cookies.
You can typically remove or reject cookies via your browser settings. Further information about cookies, including
how to see what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them,
visit www.allaboutcookies.org.
If you do not accept our cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of our Services.
Do Not Track Signals.
Some browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. We do not
currently respond to do not track signals. To find out more about "Do Not Track," please visit
http://www.allaboutdnt.com.

3. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION.
We may use your personal information as follows:
    •    To fulfill a specific request by you;
    •    To operate, maintain, and improve our Site and Services;
    •    To manage your account, including to communicate with you regarding your account with our Services;
    •    To respond to your comments and questions and to provide customer service;
    •    To send information including technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative
         messages;
    •    With your consent, to send you e-mails about upcoming events, promotions, and other news if you have
         given us consent to be added to the CampusLogic mailing list; and
    •    As we believe necessary or appropriate (a) to comply with applicable laws; (b) to comply with lawful
         requests and legal process, including to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (c) to
         enforce our Privacy Policy; and (d) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or
         others.
 At any time after opting into to receiving e-mails on the CampusLogic mailing list, you may “opt-out” by sending
 us a request at privacy@campuslogic.com. Please note that even if you opt out from receiving marketing emails,
 we may still send you non-marketing emails, which include emails about your account with us and in connection
 with your use of the Services.
 CampusLogic does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information collected through its Services
 with third parties for their sole promotional purposes.
 Sensitive Personal Data.
 CampusLogic may receive sensitive personal information about you from you or your academic institution, which
 is used solely for performing the Services authorized by your or your academic institution. You and/or your
 academic institution consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal information in accordance with
 this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal information, you
 must not submit such information through our Services.
 4. SHARING YOUR INFORMATION.
We may share your personal information as follows:
    •    Third Parties Designated by You. We may share your personal information with third parties where you
         have provided your consent to do so.
    •    Our Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your personal information with our third-party service
         providers who provide services such as information technology and related infrastructure, auditing, email
         delivery, and other similar services. These third parties are only permitted to use your personal information
         to the extent necessary to enable them to provide their services to CampusLogic.
    •    Corporate Restructuring. We may share personal information when we do a business deal, or negotiate a
         business deal, involving the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These deals can include
         any merger, financing, acquisition, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.
    •    Other Disclosures. We may share personal data as we believe necessary or appropriate: (a) to comply with
         applicable laws; (b) to comply with lawful requests and legal process, including to respond to requests from
         public and government authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; (c) to

         enforce our Policy; and (d) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others.
  5. ANONYMOUS DATA
We may create anonymous data from the personal information we receive about you and other individuals whose
personal information we collect as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Anonymous data might include analytics
information and information collected by us using cookies. We make personal information into anonymous data
by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you.
  6. THIRD PARTY SITES
  Our Site may contain links to third party websites and features. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy
  practices of such third parties. These third parties have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any
  responsibility or liability for their websites, features or policies. Please read their privacy policies before you
  submit any data to them.
  7. FEEDBACK
You may share personal information with us when you submit user generated content through our Services. Please
note that any information you post or feedback you disclose to CampusLogic through the Site or on our Services
will not be private or confidential once it is published on Site or through our Services.
If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback in our Services or on our Site without any
reference to you.
  8. YOUR RIGHTS
     •   Opt-out. You can opt out of receiving communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link or contacting us
         at privacy@campuslogic.com.
     •   Access. You may access the information we hold about you at any time via your account by contacting us
         at privacy@campuslogic.com.
     •   Amend. You can also contact us at privacy@campuslogic.com to update or correct any inaccuracies in your
         personal information.
     •   Move. You can download your documents stored in the CampusLogic Services at any time.
     •   Erase and forget. You can request that we erase your data. If you request that we erase your information,
         please note that your information may continue to reside on our backup systems.
  9. INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFER
CampusLogic is headquartered in the United States. Your personal information may be transferred, in accordance
with this Privacy Policy, outside the country in which you reside, including to the United States, where data
protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world. By
using our Site and Services and agreeing to this Privacy Policy by clicking your acceptance, you consent to this
transfer or processing of your personal information. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your
personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  10.    SECURITY

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect personal data within
our organization. Unfortunately, no transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be completely secure,
and transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. If you have reason to believe that your
interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us at
privacy@campuslogic.com.
  11.    RETENTION
We will only retain your personal data as long as reasonably required to provide you with the Services unless a
longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law.
  12.    CHILDREN
Neither our Site nor our Services are directed to children under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his
or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us directly at
privacy@campuslogic.com.
  13.    COMPLAINTS
We are committed to resolving any complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. If you
would like to make a complaint regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices in relation to your personal data, please
contact us at privacy@campuslogic.com.
  14.    PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
CampusLogic reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review
it frequently. If CampusLogic decides to change this Privacy Policy, we will post such changes to the Sites and other
places in the Applications it deems appropriate. The “Last Updated” legend above indicates when this Privacy Policy
was last changed. If we make any material changes to the Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on
our Site prior to such changes taking effect and may also notify you via email in connection with certain material
changes.
  15.    CONTACT INFORMATION
You may contact us in writing at privacy@campuslogic.com or:
CampusLogic
1340 S. Spectrum Blvd., Suite 200
Chandler, AZ 85256
Attn: Legal Department
